[music]
>> I don't have time for other lovers.
[__]
It's turned.
>> [music]
>> Give me that.
>> You could have just stepped on it.
>> I have asked the super to get an
exterminator in here, and he won't do
it. So, anytime I see a cockroach or a
spider or whatever, I try and trap it,
and then I leave it by his door.
>> Well, you really ought to get your
parents to let you borrow some money,
then you wouldn't have to live in the
third world.
>> never take money from them.
>> Because they don't have it, or because
you don't want it?
>> Because I don't want it.
>> It's Father's Day, you know.
>> It is?
>> And you should call your father.
>> I'll call him tomorrow.
>> Tomorrow, you'll be the daughter that
forgot Father's Day, instead of the one
who remembered.
Go ahead. Call him.
>> Hey, Dad.
Sorry it's so late.
Cuz you weren't home the last time I
called her.
>> There's so little she'll ever reveal to
me, or I to her. Her better half, I
know, even less.
I'm sure she's speaking half an octave
higher,
>> [music]
>> same voice she had when she was 16,
telling him all about her new job, how
much she misses him, and sorry [music]
she didn't send a card. Telling him
everything but the truth, just like she
wouldn't tell me about that young man
downstairs.
>> I'm calling now, right?
I don't want him to feel bad about it.
It was the best thing that could have
happened. I didn't [music] fit in there.
I've been called worse, Dad.
>> There's a value in having secrets.
Creatures like myself, like Claire, like
Zoe, we wouldn't be ourselves without
them.
Peter Russo, on the other hand, he's
trapped by his secrets.
What I'm trying to do is to give him the
opportunity to set himself free.
>> I don't know.
I don't know yet.
>> After all, we are nothing more or less
than what we choose to reveal. What I am
to Claire is not what I am to Zoe, just
as Zoe is not to me what she is to her
father.
>> Probably Thanksgiving.
Cuz I don't think I can make it back
before then.
Okay, I'll try.
I said I'll try.
>> Or Christmas?
>> Uh
No.
Mhm.
I'm not seeing anyone right now.
I don't feel like it.
Because I'm not interested in that.
I would tell you, Dad.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Okay.
Don't be worried about me. I'm fine.
Yeah.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Mhm.